Guide to the Cornell Electrical Engineering Centennial Symposium records,1985.
Cornell Electrical Engineering Centennial Symposium records,1985
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell Electrical Engineering Centennial Symposium records, 1985.
16-6-2512
1 v., 29 videotapes.
Videotapes.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Videotapes of sessions from the symposium and published proceedings, "Future Directions in Electrical Engineering: Proceedings of the Cornell University Electrical Engineering Centennial Symposium series, March 15-June 12, 1985," edited by Simpson Linke. Topics discussed include technological innovations in electrical engineering and electronics, social aspects of electrical engineering, space sciences, and power resources.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Videotapes of sessions from the symposium and published proceedings, "Future Directions in Electrical Engineering: Proceedings of the Cornell University Electrical Engineering Centennial Symposium series, March 15-June 12, 1985," edited by Simpson Linke. Topics discussed include technological innovations in electrical engineering and electronics, social aspects of electrical engineering, space sciences, and power resources.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Linke, Simpson, 1917-
Subjects:
Electric engineering--Technological innovations--Congresses.; Electronics--Technological innovations--Congresses.; Electric engineering--Social aspects--Congresses.; Space sciences--Congresses.; Power resources--Congresses.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Future Directions in Microelectronic - Stanford Symposium - Sporck/Broers/Eastman, Mar. 15, 1985; 1 (Box 1-3)
- Future Directions in Microelectronic - Stanford Symposium - Meindl/Hodges, Mar. 15, 1985; 2 (Box 1-3)
- Future Directions in Microelectronic - Stanford Symposium - Noyce/Howardd, Mar. 15, 1985; 3 (Box 1-3)
- Future Directions in Microelectronic - Stanford Symposium - Birnbaum/Maynard, Mar. 15, 1985; 4 (Box 1-3)
- Computers - E. Windsor, New Jersey Symposium - C. Gordon Bell - Joel Birnbaum (duplicate of 3-15 address) - Joseph Veverka (duplicate of 4-17 address), Apr. 1, 1985; 5 (Box 1-3)
- Computers - E. Windsor, New Jersey Symposium - John Cocke - Eric Nussbaum, Apr. 1, 1985; 6 (Box 1-3)
- Computers - E. Windsor, New Jersey Symposium - Andrew Hospodor - Peter Denning, Apr. 1, 1985; 7 (Box 1-3)
- Computers - E. Windsor, New Jersey Symposium - David Ahl - Fred Kahn (duplicate of 6-12 address), Apr. 1, 1985; 8 (Box 1-3)
- Communication - Boston Symposium - John Nation - James Broadhead - Robert Lucky - John Evans, Apr. 10, 1985; 9 (Box 1-3)
- Communication - Boston Symposium - Irwin Jacobs - Paul Green, Apr. 10, 1985; 10 (Box 1-3)
- Communication - Boston Symposium - Richard Blahut - G. David Forney, Apr. 10, 1985; 11 (Box 1-3)
- Communication - Boston Symposium - Frank Rhodes (duplicate of 6-12) - Pearce Williams (duplicate of 6-11), Apr. 10, 1985; 12 (Box 1-3)
- Cornell Symposium: Weather and Climate Prediction, A View of the Future - Wilmot Hess, Apr. 17, 1985; 13 (Box 1-3)
- Cornell Symposium: The MST Radar Technique - Ben Balsley, Apr. 17, 1985; 14 (Box 1-3)
- Cornell Symposium: Atmospheric Remote Sensing - C. Gordon Little, Apr. 17, 1985; 15 (Box 1-3)
- Cornell Symposium: A Giant Step for Mankind - Communications - William Gordon, Apr. 17, 1985; 16 (Box 1-3)
- Cornell Symposium: The Arecibo Observatory - Tors Hagfors, Apr. 17, 1985; 17 (Box 1-3)
- Cornell Symposium: Exploring the Outer Solar System - Joseph Veverka, Apr. 17, 1985; 18 (Box 1-3)
- Energy Symposium - Washington, D.C. - Ravindra Sudan - Joseph Ballantyne - Donald Kerr - Eric Wilis - Jack Vanderryn - Robert Hirsch, Apr. 25, 1985; 19 (Box 1-3)
- Energy Symposium - Washington, D.C. - Robert Hirsch - Harold Furth - Milton Klein, Apr. 25, 1985; 20 (Box 1-3)
- Energy Symposium - Washington, D.C. - Milton Klein - Gerald Wilson - Alvin Trivelpiece, Apr. 25, 1985; 21 (Box 1-3)
- L. Pearce Williams - Edited Master 1 of 2, June 11, 1985; 22 (Box 1-3)
- L. Pearce Williams - Edited Master 2 of 2, June 11, 1985; 23 (Box 1-3)
- Ithaca, N.Y. - Societal Impacts and Future Directions - Dale Corson - John Nation - Hans Bethe, June 12, 1985; 24 (Box 1-3)
- Ithaca, N.Y. - Societal Impacts and Future Directions - Hans Bethe (cont'd) - Fred Kahn, June 12, 1985; 25 (Box 1-3)
- Ithaca, N.Y. - Societal Impacts and Future Directions - Fred Kahn (cont'd) - Maurice Bernard, June 12, 1985; 26 (Box 1-3)
- Ithaca, N.Y. - Societal Impacts and Future Directions - Maurice Bernard (cont'd) - Lewis Branscomb, June 12, 1985; 27 (Box 1-3)
- Ithaca, N.Y. - Societal Impacts and Future Directions - Sol Buchsbaum, June 12, 1985; 28 (Box 1-3)
- Ithaca, N.Y. - Societal Impacts and Future Directions - Frank Rhodes, June 12, 1985; 29 (Box 1-3)